Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=The Ascent of Ling Yun=
=صعود لينغ يون=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
(Ling Yun's Rainy Night Meeting with a Guard Exposed)
(كشف لقاء لينغ يون مع الحارس في ليلة ممطرة)
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I don't understand something.
انا لا افهم شيئا.
Your brother is the esteemed General of Jingyuan.
أخوك هو الجنرال الموقر لجينغيوان.
How could the emperor's personal maid be worthy of him?
كيف يمكن لخادمة الإمبراطور الشخصية أن تكون جديرة به؟
Wouldn't it benefit that wretch?
ألا ينفع هذا الوغد؟
Do you truly believe I want her to become my brother's concubine
هل تعتقد حقًا أنني أريدها أن تصبح محظية أخي؟
so she can live a life of luxury ever after?
حتى تتمكن من عيش حياة فاخرة إلى الأبد؟
She can dream on.
إنها قادرة على الاستمرار في الحلم.
Keep watch on her the next few days.
راقبها في الأيام القليلة القادمة.
That wretch has many tricks up her sleeve.
تلك الوغد لديها الكثير من الحيل في جعبتها.
Mark my words.
تذكر كلامي.
She'll likely seize the first chance
من المرجح أن تغتنم الفرصة الأولى
to crawl into my brother's bed.
للزحف إلى سرير أخي.
Understood.
مفهومة.
But Your Highness,
ولكن صاحب السمو،
if that should happen,
إذا حدث ذلك،
aren't you afraid it'll
ألا تخاف من ذلك؟
implicate your brother?
توريط أخيك؟
My brother is a national hero.
أخي هو بطل قومي.
His Majesty won't jeopardize the peace
جلالته لن يعرض السلام للخطر
for the sake of a mere maid.
من أجل مجرد خادمة.
Moreover, in such matters,
وعلاوة على ذلك، في مثل هذه الأمور،
women always bear the consequences.
المرأة تتحمل العواقب دائمًا.
As for men,
أما بالنسبة للرجال،
they just add another romantic anecdote to their list.
إنهم يضيفون فقط حكاية رومانسية أخرى إلى قائمتهم.
Zhao Yanwan lives in Chengxi Palace now
يعيش Zhao Yanwan في قصر Chengxi الآن
and is acting superior as the Zhaos' legitimate daughter.
وتتصرف كرئيسة للإبنة الشرعية لعائلة تشاو.
I should have
كان ينبغي لي أن
ordered someone
أمر شخص ما
to paint her singing routines from her southern days.
لرسم روتيناتها الغنائية من أيامها الجنوبية.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Consort Wan instigated General Zhao to request the emperor's personal maid.
حثت الزوجة وان الجنرال تشاو على طلب الخادمة الشخصية للإمبراطور.
If this should anger His Majesty,
إذا كان هذا من شأنه أن يغضب جلالته،
General Zhao could face repercussions.
قد يواجه الجنرال تشاو عواقب وخيمة.
You show such concern for my brother.
لقد أظهرت اهتماما كبيرا بأخي.
Do you also
هل انت ايضا
aspire to be his concubine?
تطمح أن تكون محظيته؟
I wouldn't dare.
لا أجرؤ على ذلك.
I once received General Zhao's kindness.
لقد تلقيت لطف الجنرال تشاو ذات مرة.
My only concern is for Your Highness and General Zhao.
اهتمامي الوحيد هو سموكم والجنرال تشاو.
I harbor no ulterior motives.
ليس لدي أي دوافع خفية.
Rise.
يعلو.
You're correct.
أنت على حق.
Zhao Yanwan
تشاو يانوان
schemes ruthlessly to stir trouble for favor.
يخططون بلا رحمة لإثارة المشاكل من أجل الحصول على الود.
She'll eventually ruin our family.
إنها سوف تدمر عائلتنا في نهاية المطاف.
Now she can't even defeat a mere maid.
الآن لم تعد قادرة حتى على هزيمة خادمة.
I must devise a way
يجب أن أبتكر طريقة
to eliminate Ling Yun.
للقضاء على لينغ يون.
I won't let them bring harm to my brother.
لن أسمح لهم بإيذاء أخي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
taking personal action against that Ling Yun wretch
اتخاذ إجراءات شخصية ضد ذلك الوغد لينغ يون
would be honoring her too much.
سيكون تكريمًا لها كثيرًا.
After dealing with Ling Yun,
بعد التعامل مع لينغ يون،
I'll settle accounts properly with Zhao Yanwan.
سأقوم بتسوية الحسابات بشكل صحيح مع تشاو يانوان.
The next few days,
الأيام القليلة القادمة،
have someone monitor that wretch's movements.
اطلب من شخص ما مراقبة تحركات هذا الوغد.
Understood.
مفهومة.
(Night Watch Post, Taiping Gate)
(مركز الحراسة الليلية، بوابة تايبينغ)
Will you assist me?
هل ستساعدني؟
I wish to request
أريد أن أطلب
a copy of the night duty roster for Taiping Gate's military officers.
نسخة من سجل الخدمة الليلية لضباط الجيش في بوابة تايبينغ.
Who are you, young eunuch?
من أنت أيها الشاب الخصي؟
Raise your head.
ارفع رأسك
Miss? It's you!
آنسة؟ أنت!
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
I was merely passing by.
لقد كنت مجرد أمر.
I've disturbed your peace.
لقد أزعجت سلامك.
I'll take my leave.
سوف آخذ إجازتي.
Coming to Taiping Gate at night dressed like this,
عند القدوم إلى بوابة تايبينغ في الليل مرتديًا مثل هذا الزي،
you said you were passing by?
قلت أنك كنت تمر؟
General,
عام،
why feign ignorance
لماذا نتظاهر بالجهل
and humiliate me?
وتذلني؟
General, please let me go.
سيدي الجنرال، من فضلك اسمح لي بالذهاب.
People might see us.
قد يرانا الناس.
General,
عام،
let me go.
دعني أذهب.
Promise me
وعدني
you'll visit me again,
سوف تزورني مرة أخرى
and I'll let go.
وسوف اتركه يذهب.
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
The Tiankui Revitalizing Incense
بخور تيانكوي المنعش
is rationed to three qian per month for the harem consorts,
يتم توزيعها على ثلاث تشيان شهريًا لزوجات الحريم،
but should you need it,
ولكن إذا كنت في حاجة إليها،
simply give the order
فقط أعط الأمر
no matter the quantity.
بغض النظر عن الكمية.
No, no.
لا لا.
Lady Ling Yun,
السيدة لينغ يون،
I dare not accept your silver.
لا أجرؤ على قبول فضتك.
You serve before His Majesty.
أنت تخدم أمام جلالته.
I must beg your favor
يجب أن أطلب صالحك
to speak well of me in the future.
للتحدث عني بشكل جيد في المستقبل.
Sir Eunuch,
سيدي الخصي،
I shall certainly mention
سأذكر بالتأكيد
your diligent service to His Majesty.
خدمتكم الدؤوبة لجلالته.
Please accept the silver.
يرجى قبول الفضة.
We all serve our masters.
نحن جميعا نخدم أسيادنا.
None have it easy.
لا أحد لديه الأمر سهلا.
Take the surplus silver
خذ الفائض من الفضة
for some wine money.
من أجل بعض المال للنبيذ.
Thank you for your consideration.
شكرا لاهتمامكم.
Then
ثم
I will take it.
سوف آخذها.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I have uncovered new information.
لقد اكتشفت معلومات جديدة.
Ling Yun posed as a eunuch
لينغ يون يتظاهر بأنه خصي
to secretly meet General Zhao at Taiping Gate two nights ago.
للقاء الجنرال تشاو سراً في بوابة تايبينغ قبل ليلتين.
Yesterday, she visited
لقد زارت أمس
Imperial Household Department
قسم البلاط الإمبراطوري
and spent six months' wages
وأنفقت أجور ستة أشهر
to buy Tiankui Revitalizing Incense.
لشراء بخور تيانكوي المنعش.
Today,
اليوم،
that very incense burns on General Wansong's desk.
هذا البخور يحترق على مكتب الجنرال وانسونغ.
How laughable!
كم هو مضحك!
She actually gifted Tiankui Incense to my brother?
هل هي في الواقع أهدت بخور تيانكوي لأخي؟
This premium incense
هذا البخور الممتاز
is rationed at three qian per month for harem consorts.
يتم توزيعها بمعدل ثلاثة تشيان شهريا لزوجات الحريم.
Even with money,
حتى مع المال،
one can't obtain extra.
لا يمكن الحصول على المزيد.
That wretch
هذا الوغد
has invested heavily
لقد استثمرت بكثافة
to ensnare my brother.
للإيقاع بأخي.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
It seems that wretch
يبدو أن البائس
genuinely aspires to become General Wansong's concubine.
تطمح حقًا إلى أن تصبح محظية الجنرال وان سونغ.
Her doom approaches.
مصيرها يقترب.
Let her cling to her delusions a little longer.
دعوها تتمسك بأوهامها لفترة أطول قليلا.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
you've reviewed memorials for four hours straight.
لقد قمت بمراجعة النصب التذكارية لمدة أربع ساعات متواصلة.
State affairs matter,
شؤون الدولة مهمة
but your imperial health matters equally.
لكن صحتك الإمبراطورية مهمة بنفس القدر.
Please have some tea.
من فضلك تناول بعض الشاي.
Unexplained kindness.
لطف غير مفهوم.
What are you up to?
ما آخر ما توصلت اليه؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
do you remember
هل تذكر
my promise to ensure
وعدي بضمان ذلك
your restful sleep free from insomnia?
نومك المريح خالي من الأرق؟
I recall
انا اتذكر
someone's bold claim
ادعاء جريء لشخص ما
to discipline arrogant officials for me
لتأديب المسؤولين المتغطرسين من أجلي
and guarantee my sound sleep.
وأضمن نومي السليم.
Today
اليوم
marks the day to fulfill that promise.
يصادف اليوم تحقيق هذا الوعد.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Put on this rain cloak.
ارتدي معطف المطر هذا.
I'll take you somewhere.
سأأخذك إلى مكان ما.
This is a guard's attire.
هذا هو لباس الحارس.
I am the emperor.
أنا الإمبراطور.
How can I wear such garments?
كيف يمكنني أن أرتدي مثل هذه الملابس؟
It's raining outside,
إنها تمطر في الخارج
and we're pressed for time.
ونحن مضغوطون من حيث الوقت.
I could only procure these.
لم أتمكن من الحصول إلا على هذه.
Please put them on and follow me.
من فضلك ارتديهم واتبعني.
Ling Yun,
لينغ يون,
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Ling Yun?
لينغ يون؟
Ling Yun,
لينغ يون,
where exactly are you taking me?
إلى أين تأخذني بالضبط؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
this opportunity is rare.
هذه الفرصة نادرة.
Just trust me.
فقط ثق بي.
You'll know shortly.
سوف تعرف قريبا.
Support me properly.
ادعمني بشكل صحيح.
How could you answer
كيف يمكنك الإجابة؟
if I'm harmed?
إذا تعرضت للأذى؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
do you suffer from night blindness?
هل تعاني من العمى الليلي؟
Why keep stepping in puddles?
لماذا تستمر في الخطو في البرك؟
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Silence now.
الصمت الآن.
Rest assured,
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك،
I will keep your secret.
سأحافظ على سرك.
Yanwan,
يانوان،
Hui Zhi saw Ling Yun
رأى هوي تشى لينغ يون
and a guard-dressed man sneaking
ورجل يرتدي زي حارس يتسلل
into the Imperial Garden together.
إلى الحديقة الإمبراطورية معًا.
Really?
حقًا؟
That wretch is very cunning.
هذا الوغد ماكر جدًا.
Are you certain?
هل انت متأكد؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I saw clearly.
لقد رأيت بوضوح.
It was Ling Yun.
لقد كان لينغ يون.
The guard wore a rain cloak.
كان الحارس يرتدي معطفا واقيا من المطر.
They behaved intimately
لقد تصرفوا بشكل حميم
and acted furtively.
وتصرفت خلسة.
With the ongoing rain,
مع استمرار هطول الأمطار،
the Imperial Garden stands deserted,
الحديقة الإمبراطورية تقف مهجورة،
perfect for clandestine meetings.
مثالية للاجتماعات السرية.
(The fish bit the hook.)
(عضت السمكة الخطاف.)
(Time to reel in the net.)
(حان وقت صيد السمك في الشبكة.)
If it's a clandestine meeting,
إذا كان اجتماعا سريا،
let's capitalize on this,
دعونا نستفيد من هذا،
catch her in the act,
القبض عليها متلبسة
and eliminate her for good.
والقضاء عليها نهائيا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's find out
دعونا نكتشف
how His Majesty's personal maid
كيف كانت خادمة جلالته الشخصية
is carrying out an affair with a guard.
يقوم بعلاقة غرامية مع حارس.
Go bring that guard
اذهب واحضر هذا الحارس
to the Fourteen Bureaus.
إلى المكاتب الأربعة عشر.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Proceed with caution later.
المضي بحذر في وقت لاحق.
We mustn't let her escape again.
لا يجب أن نسمح لها بالهروب مرة أخرى.
Consort Wan,
القرينة وان،
I saw it clearly.
لقد رأيته بوضوح.
Ling Yun was holding the guard's hand tightly.
كان لينغ يون يمسك بيد الحارس بإحكام.
This time,
هذه المرة،
she won't escape.
انها لن تهرب.
Ling Yun,
لينغ يون,
it's late at night.
إنه وقت متأخر من الليل.
Why did you bring me to the boat?
لماذا أحضرتني إلى القارب؟
Shh.
ششش.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
listen.
يستمع.
When I was young,
عندما كنت صغيرا،
I lived with my parents in Jiangnan.
لقد عشت مع والدي في جيانجنان.
We stayed in a boathouse
لقد بقينا في بيت القوارب
for some time.
لبعض الوقت.
On rainy nights,
في الليالي الممطرة،
I'd hear raindrops pattering on the boat canopy,
كنت أسمع صوت قطرات المطر وهي تتساقط على سقف القارب،
rustling softly.
حفيف ناعم.
The gentle dripping sounds
أصوات التنقيط اللطيفة
would lull me into sleep.
سوف يساعدني على النوم.
Soon I'd be sound asleep.
سوف أكون نائما قريبا.
Since then,
منذ ذلك الحين،
I've known
لقد عرفت
no matter how troubled my heart,
مهما كان قلبي مضطربًا،
a rainy night always brings
ليلة ممطرة تجلب دائما
restful sleep.
نوم مريح.
I've never had
لم يكن لدي قط
such experiences.
مثل هذه التجارب.
Yet hearing you,
ومع ذلك أسمعك،
I can already sense
أنا أستطيع أن أشعر بالفعل
that serenity
هذا السكينة
and comfort.
والراحة.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
I heard of your sleepless nights.
لقد سمعت عن لياليك التي لم تنام فيها.
I kept thinking
بقيت أفكر
I must find a way
يجب أن أجد طريقة
to bring Your Majesty to this boat on a rainy night
لإحضار جلالتك إلى هذا القارب في ليلة ممطرة
to let the rain's rhythm
للسماح لإيقاع المطر
grant you peaceful slumber.
أمنحك نومًا هادئًا.
So you can recover your energy
حتى تتمكن من استعادة طاقتك
while also experiencing
بينما تعاني أيضا
the comfort and joy of my childhood.
راحة وفرح طفولتي.
Your Highness!
صاحب السمو!
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I've investigated.
لقد قمت بالتحقيق.
General Zhao was supposed to be on watch tonight.
كان من المفترض أن يكون الجنرال تشاو في حالة تأهب الليلة.
But now, he's not
لكن الآن، فهو ليس كذلك
at Taiping Gate.
عند بوابة تايبينغ.
No one knows where he is.
لا أحد يعرف أين هو.
That wretch!
هذا الوغد!
She won't escape now.
انها لن تهرب الآن.
How audacious!
كم هي جريئة!
Daring to meet in the Imperial Garden
الجرأة على اللقاء في الحديقة الإمبراطورية
for such lewd acts!
لمثل هذه الأفعال الفاحشة!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's board the boat
دعونا نصعد على متن القارب
to catch them in the act.
للقبض عليهم متلبسين.